(Sheldon:)No.
(Ira:)Now, Dr. Hofstadter.
(Ira:)Can you walk us
through the process
(Ira:)you used to disprove his theory?
(Sheldon:)-Well...
-I believe I can answer that.
(Leonard:)He asked me.
(Leonard:)Fine.
(Leonard:)As I was saying...
(Sheldon:)You're telling it wrong.
Ira...
(Sheldon:)...to really understand the story here,
(Sheldon:)you have to start
at the very beginning.
(Sheldon:)A small town in East Texas,
where a young genius named...
(Ira Flatow:)-Sheldon...
-That's right, Sheldon Cooper.
(Sheldon:)He was bitten by his neighbour's dog,
(Sheldon:)leading to his first
scientific breakthrough,
(Sheldon:)the doggie death-ray.
(Sheldon:)Which, sadly, he couldn't build
(Sheldon:)because Santa wouldn't bring
him enriched uranium.
(Ira:)You know, I'd really like
to hear it from Dr. Hofstadter,
if ifs okay with you.
(Sheldon:)What a surprise.
(Sheldon:)Did you invite me back
just so you could ignore me?
(Ira:)Actually, I didn't invite you.
(Ira:)You came in, you took a seat,
(Ira:)and I'm not comfortable
with confrontation.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, this interview
is supposed to be about me.
(Sheldon:)Well, that seems
like a snooze.
(Sheldon:)Even for public radio.
(Sheldon:)You know,
if we did a shot every time
(Penny(listening in her apartment):)they said something embarrassing,
(Penny(listening in her apartment):)this would be one hell
of a drinking game.
(Amy:)A little early for alcohol, isn't it?
(Sheldon:)You know, I don't just say
smart things about science.
(Sheldon:)I also yodel.
I (SHELDON YODELING) I
(Amy:)I'll get the vodka.